[{"answer": "No.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "Jack, am I going to die here?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "Yes, yes --", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "These are baby tigers, right?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Well, I'll tell you about another 20 months.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "At what age can they kill a man?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "No, it's not a matter of -- you know, that's a good question.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "Why are you not remotely scared of them?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "But that tongue -- you see how is licking me?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "Like sand paper beyond you've ever seen.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Maybe 200 to 400, that's all.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "How -- I mean, when they get to the full size -- how many of these are there left in the world?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Well this is a special diet we have for the -- for the cats.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "What do you feed them with?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "I did hear that little growling.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "You heard that little growling there, right?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "All right.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Now, we're going to bring on -- now, what is this?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "If they get down in the grass -- I have only seen these twice in the wild.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Ten feet?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Jack, he wants to eat your hand.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "See the spots?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "No, right now, as far as tame, this animal won't become a tame animal.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "How tame are these by comparison to a purely wild version?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "This is an Egyptian vulture.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "OK, this is the vulture?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "You're actually feeding the vulture raw meat?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "It stinks.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "You smell that?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Well, one good thing is, they keep the earth -", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Tell me one good thing about the vulture?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Now, remember you do the story with me --", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "What's this?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "About alligators killing people, yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "-- two months ago, right?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "You want to go at that?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "If you look there, they've got two eyelids.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "What do you mean a nice one?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "I don't mean nice.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "How do you tell a nice alligator?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "ANNA: They have two eyelids.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "Huh?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Yes, but he's not going to right now.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "This could kill me, right?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "I don't know that for sure, but I don't think he should.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "How do you know?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "No, I haven't lately.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "He's going to show you -- if you have ever seen alligators -- down his throat?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "There's no throat.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "You can see down the throat like most animals, right?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Curly.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "What's his name?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "Oh gosh!", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "How old do they live to be?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Yes and no.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "I mean, would they attack if they're not challenged or scared?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "The male is hot.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "I'm not sure if the male's hot or -- what is it?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Ever found human remains inside of Curly?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "I don't want to hold Curly.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "You want to hold it?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "I'm demonstrating how the eyes are fixed on movement and how they don't want to hurt anyone.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "What are you doing?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "This is -- yes, people don't realize it.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Quite a few.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "How many penguins are left in the world?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "My wife.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "What is your favorite animal?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "You know, having raised animals all my life for 50- something years, I would say that you know, I'm fascinated by cats.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "But if I could say look, Jack, you'll live the rest of your life on a desert island with one animal, what would it be?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "A one!", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "What would you have?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Well, it's a second-largest mammal in the world.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Quite something else, isn't it?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Jimmy.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "What's his name?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "They're both very slow on what it will do, right?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "Yes, they really are.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "He's magnificent, isn't he?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Put that one of there.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "What's this?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "No wonder you get to hold -- how did you even pick the thing up?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "Oh, this one here.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Who would win if they had a fight?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Two hundred.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "You know, these things can leave over 100 -- as a matter of fact what it was 200 years?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "ANNA: No food, nothing.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "No water, no food?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "He's heavy, right?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "Well last night one was crawling around the hotel room, and he was like crossing room like a 10 second.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "How fast can they actually move if they really want to?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "You ain't seen nothing.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "You have them in your hotel room?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Yes, we've got -- we've got --", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "No but --", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Jack, are you slightly mad?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Wait, let me finish the wallaby.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "What is that?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "You do it.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Who is this?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "A laughing kookaburra from Australia.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "What is this?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "That's hilarious.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "Oh, really, doesn't that crack you up?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "This right here is a three-banded armadillo.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "What is this?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "That's a joke.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Did you say there'll be batteries in it?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "A three-banded armadillo.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "What is this?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "I'm just telling you.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "What do you mean you hope?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "Well, some people say a thousand, some people -- I've heard 500 because they live in altitudes, as you know, way up there in the Himalayas.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "How many are left in the world?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "Well, that's just it.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "Where there are so few of them, how do they find another one to mate with?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Can they mix mate with other breeds?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "That was very cool.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "That was cool, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Oh, the colder, the better for this cat.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "He likes to operate in the cold, right?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "Well, we keep, we always keep him in air-conditioning wherever the cat goes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "So how does he deal with, you know, being in New York and what is a reasonably high temperature?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "In the hotel room.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "Where do you keep him at night?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "I'm dead serious, yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "Are you serious?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "Not much during the night.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "Do you sleep?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "This coat, the sad thing about this coat, Piers, on the black market, this coat right now, if you can even find one, a guy got caught in Europe last year, $80,000.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Not at all?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "This coat right here.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "For this coat?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "See, that's a tragedy, isn't it?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "But you ever touch a beaver?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "Oh, he wants more to eat, yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "Is it happy with that apple, or is he looking for something a little bit more meaty?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 679, "question": "Do they eat meat?", "qSentId": 678}, {"answer": "I can smell it.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 688, "question": "Can you smell him?", "qSentId": 687}, {"answer": "No, it was me.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "Did he go to the bathroom?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "Yes, the whole thumb here, the whole thing, yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 696, "question": "But a beaver like this nearly bit your finger off, right?", "qSentId": 695}, {"answer": "One of the worst yes, yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "The worst injury you've had?", "qSentId": 698}, {"answer": "I think so, yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "So -- do you have beavers in England?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "Now, what you have here is very rare.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "What have we got here?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "Yes, because he's -- water can come from what he eats.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 732, "question": "Without ever drinking water?", "qSentId": 731}, {"answer": "Yes, the mother died.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "Both of these, right?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 748, "question": "But, yes, when you say, cunning like a fox, you've heard that term, cunning like a fox?", "qSentId": 747}, {"answer": "Yes, and if you are ever asked the question on a game show, again, you can give me half the money if you get this.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 757, "question": "The biggest owl in the world?", "qSentId": 756}, {"answer": "Silent flight.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 790, "question": "It's completely silent?", "qSentId": 789}, {"answer": "Right, the monster is still here, but there is a chance that the victory may be in Congress's hands.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 827, "question": "Where do we stand now?", "qSentId": 826}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 844, "question": "Two miles?", "qSentId": 843}, {"answer": "All right.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 872, "question": "How would this kill (inaudible)?", "qSentId": 871}, {"answer": "So this animal has a tough time in nature.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 879, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 878}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 881, "question": "The lion will kill the cheetah?", "qSentId": 880}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 883, "question": "And eat it?", "qSentId": 882}, {"answer": "King of the beasts, he can kill just about anything, maybe he'd be a tough time with the elephant.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 886, "question": "Can the lion kill anything basically?", "qSentId": 885}, {"answer": "Yes, oh, yes, unless she has her cubs, which they will have in three to four years.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 893, "question": "So they prefer to be alone?", "qSentId": 892}, {"answer": "Well, because, these folks -- (inaudible) making sure.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 900, "question": "How can your trainers be so relaxed?", "qSentId": 899}, {"answer": "Oh, this thing here.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 916, "question": "Who would win?", "qSentId": 915}, {"answer": "Oh, it's just -- when we film, it's three cameras.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 919, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 918}, {"answer": "ANNA: Well, the peregrine falcon, the only one at 200 -- that's a bird, by the way.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 924, "question": "There's no faster animal in the world than this?", "qSentId": 923}, {"answer": "No, we won't.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 942, "question": "What makes you think there will be a next time?", "qSentId": 941}, {"answer": "Yes, (inaudible).", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 954, "question": "And he's a very ugly animal, isn't he, Jack?", "qSentId": 953}, {"answer": "(Inaudible) he's drinking a lot now.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 969, "question": "How much milk do they drink a day?", "qSentId": 968}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 995, "question": "You're going to catch him?", "qSentId": 994}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1003, "question": "What is this?", "qSentId": 1002}, {"answer": "Well, yes, but then again, they raise the animals.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1029, "question": "Do your guys never get bitten or anything?", "qSentId": 1028}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1035, "question": "Have you ever touched a bear?", "qSentId": 1034}, {"answer": "Someone told me that.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1052, "question": "Can you feel that?", "qSentId": 1051}, {"answer": "It's extraordinary.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1057, "question": "Can you imagine that?", "qSentId": 1056}, {"answer": "SARS, yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1062, "question": "But this animal here is also -- if you remember the SARS disease, you remember about 10 years in Asia, it killed people, SARS?", "qSentId": 1061}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1131, "question": "He runs flat on that?", "qSentId": 1130}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1193, "question": "Is he feeling that I'm hot, then, because (inaudible)?", "qSentId": 1192}, {"answer": "That's what he's doing, he's feeling the warm particles coming off you with that tongue.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1199, "question": "What's that tongue doing?", "qSentId": 1198}, {"answer": "Well, then he might want to --", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1201, "question": "What does he want to do then?", "qSentId": 1200}, {"answer": "Well, just get something to eat.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1203, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 1202}, {"answer": "Well, just bit --", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1205, "question": "How?", "qSentId": 1204}, {"answer": "Well, he just bites you.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1207, "question": "What does a lizard do?", "qSentId": 1206}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1212, "question": "-- Komodo dragon, right?", "qSentId": 1211}, {"answer": "Well, they -- a lot of them are obviously eaten by snakes and there are birds of prey or whatever it might.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1237, "question": "See, how do nice cuddly little things like this survive in the wild?", "qSentId": 1236}, {"answer": "It's just a little dirt.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1251, "question": "What is it doing?", "qSentId": 1250}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1254, "question": "You sure?", "qSentId": 1253}, {"answer": "No, (inaudible).", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1274, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 1273}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1287, "question": "What's this?", "qSentId": 1286}, {"answer": "Keep his head over this way.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1291, "question": "Where?", "qSentId": 1290}, {"answer": "The anaconda, they have about 200 teeth that are shaped like fish hooks.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1298, "question": "You've got an anaconda wrapped around your neck, are you mad?", "qSentId": 1297}, {"answer": "Not now, Jack.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1304, "question": "Piers?", "qSentId": 1303}, {"answer": "He's smelling you right now.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1309, "question": "But what is he doing right now?", "qSentId": 1308}, {"answer": "Just feels your heat.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1311, "question": "What does that mean?", "qSentId": 1310}, {"answer": "No, but what he does, Piers, hey, remember something, this snake here gets to be almost 25 to 30 feet long in the -- he's a water snake.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1313, "question": "Before a kill or what?", "qSentId": 1312}, {"answer": "Because he can't kill me and he knows that.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1321, "question": "Why is it around your neck?", "qSentId": 1320}, {"answer": "He's just too big.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1324, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 1323}, {"answer": "Yes, this animal knows that this -- this is an animal.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1327, "question": "(Inaudible) it knows he can't kill him?", "qSentId": 1326}, {"answer": "It's (inaudible).", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1339, "question": "They will do what comes naturally?", "qSentId": 1338}, {"answer": "Well, we may never be back.", "docId": "121230pmt", "aSentId": 1346, "question": "You know what, Jack?", "qSentId": 1345}]